(Penny:)Hey, you're up early.
(Sheldon:)I couldn't sleep.
(Penny:)I told you those Walking Dead
pillowcases were a bad idea.
(Sheldon:)No, that's not it.
(Penny:)Is something bothering you?
(Sheldon:)Yes, but you wouldn't understand.
(Penny:)Come on, try me.
(Sheldon:)All right.
(Sheldon:)I've devoted the prime
of my life to string theory
(Sheldon:)and its quest for the
compactification of extra dimensions.
(Sheldon:)I've got nothing to show for it,
and I feel like a fool.
OK. I get it.
(Penny:)I mean, not all the jibber-jabber
in the middle, but...
(Penny:)...I know what it's like to put your
heart and soul into something
(Penny:)and get nothing out of it.
(Sheldon:)You mean your acting career?
(Raj:)-No.
-Your relationship with Leonard?
(Raj:)No.
(Sheldon:)Your failed attempt
to go back to college?
No!